casearch.ca 2011-03-01

# Shopping

We at casearch take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

casearch respects and protects the privacy of the individuals that use our Individually identifiable information about you is not disclosed to any third party as explained in this privacy policy ("Privacy Statement").

### What Information Do We Collect?

casearch does not collect any unique information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information in the form of an email.

### Links to Other Sites

The sites displayed as search results or linked to by casearch are developed by people over whom casearch exercises no control. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information.

### With Whom Does casearch Share Information?

casearch will not share information about you with any advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties.

### Is casearch Adware, Spyware or Malware?

casearch does not monitor, collect data or 'spy' on its user base. Any software program that is implying or reporting that casearch is 'adware', 'spyware' or 'malware' is incorrect. casearch is incapable of tracking your overall web use or deciphering anything on your hard drive. casearch does not display pop-ups or any type of advertising.

### How does casearch make any money?

Some of the search engines listed in the casearch may pay a listing fee or may share revenue from advertising within the search results (sponsored links).

### Your consent and changes to the Privacy Policy

casearch may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

### Questions and Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions, please Contact Us or you can mail us at: info@casearch.com
